Oh, no!
Looks like I win again!
Come on, Leafy. We have to play again. I have to win this time!
Uh, I-I don't know, Firey. I hadn't planned on
playing Tic-Tac-Toe seventy-three times today.
Come on, Leafy, please!
Uh, actually, y-yeah, let's do it!
- ROCKY: Bleh!
- Oh, my gosh! Rocky just threw up!
He might be sick! We have to go help him! NOW!
FIREY:
Hey, wait! Leafy! Come back!
- AAAAAAAAAAA!!!!
- Leafy! Leafy! Oh, no, what happened?
EEEAAAHHH!!
- Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! What's happening!?
- AAAHHH!
ROCKY:
Bleh!
Hey! I'm weightless!
Wow!
Hey, Radio? Why are we in space?
Because of budget cuts.
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Subtitles: Daniel Adam Valle
Hey, Ice Cube, look! It's the Big Dipper!
This star is for you!
Thanks!
Huh? Oh, no, what happened to the Big Dipper?!
And why are Bubble and Ice Cube playing catch?!
Be quiet. Even though we are in
space, everything is still the same.
So we will still have Cake at Stake.
♪ The points are gone ♪
♪ We are free of them now, but we look on ♪
♪ To the moment that we see: ♪
♪ The next slice of cake ♪
♪ A step closer to the prize ♪
♪ Brought on by Cake at Stake ♪
Well, I learned that a normal cake
would explode in the vacuum of space.
So instead, I got an ice cream cake.
Yum!
Wait, how would that make any difference?
Hush!
If you get cake, you are safe.
Otherwise, you are eliminated.
Bubble, Rocky, Firey, and Leafy
had immunity, so they get cake.
I know you love ice cream cake,
Bubble, so I'm giving you my cake!
Thanks!
Now it's down to David, Spongy, and Ice Cube.
545 people voted this time.
Seventy-two of them voted for Ice Cube, she is safe.
So it's either Spongy or David to leave the game.
Both entered the game late. Let's show the votes.
Hey, where's the drum roll?
It was too annoying.
Then I'll make my own.
Bedededelluhmm... eh-
PBPBPBPBPBPBPBPBpbpbpbpbpbpb...
[GASP!] KSSHHHHH!
Spongy gets a cake...
Yaaay!
...and David is eliminated.
Aw, seriously?!
Whoa! That-that was just-
Yes, it was our double
laser-powered teleportation device.
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Wait, we already played that, didn't we?
Well, yeah, you did. But let's play it
again, you know, for good measure.
♪ [INTRO PLAYS] ♪
Wow, Firey! It's such a
relief that David's eliminated.
Definitely.
He was weird.
I know! He looked a lot
like a human, whatever that is.
You know, Firey, I think we should be friends!
You mean, like, form an alliance?
No! Friends, j-just friends, friends.
Yeah! We could do that.
Let's do it!
I want to be friends, too.
Gah! Get away!
Why are you excluding me? I just want to be friends.
Sorry, only good people get to be friends.
Ooh! Burn!
Anyway, I'm giving all of you immunity.
However, it is possible for you to lose your immunity.
- And how could that happen?
- Oh, you could be hit by an asteroid.
Or abducted by aliens, to name a few.
ROCKY:
Bleh!
Moving on...
The twentieth contest is to
get into a spaceship. Go.
Hueughauuugh!
- Hup! Did it!
Ah! Oh, no! I can't get in!
If you get hit by anything, you lose your immunity.
Yikes!
Aaaghueughehhh!
Hey, Fir-AYE! Let's go get Spongy!
Yeah!
SPONGY:
Huh?
Huh-whoa! Whoa! Whoa-ughuoahooaaaaughhugh!
Whoa-whoa-WHOA-urghruoah!
We're not getting him, Leafy!
Time for super-speed mode!
But don't you know how much energy that wastes?
- You have to be more eco-friendly, I mean-
- SPONGY: Grr!
Oh, no! Leafy! No!
Huh? Why am I moving?
Oh, my gosh! What's that?
Falling into that black hole will also
cause you to lose your immunity.
BUBBLE:
Oh noio!
SPONGY:
Uh-oh.
AAAAAAHHHHH!
HAAAAEUUUH!
WAAAAUUGH!
Hey! Where'd it go?
We had to sell it because of budget cuts.
Weird. Hey, where'd my spaceship go?
Same thing.
Oh, well, I still have MINE!
And Bubble wins immunity.
YOYLECAKE!
Now, let's recover the lost contestants.
Bubble, as another reward, you get to choose
another person to also have immunity.
Oh, uh, okay. Uh...give it to Leafy
to prove to her that I am a nice person after all...
AGAIN!!!
Twice in a row? That's quite nice.
Ooh, yay! Quite nice is a lot
better than what I got last time!
Well, it is better, but not by much.
You still got seventy-three more levels to go
before you reach my level of niceness.
Oh! Awh...
That means Bubble and Leafy have immunity,
while Ice Cube, Rocky, Spongy,
and Firey are up for elimination.
And guess what?
The fifteen eliminated contestants
will get to choose who to eliminate.
And they will have one month to decide.
[GASP!]
Do you hear that, voters? That means
you will vote on something else.
And what would this something else be?
You see, an eliminated contestant's
going to rejoin the game.
[GASP!]
For the last time in BFDI, ever.
And the voters will decide who it is.
[GASP!]
Oh, be quiet, you gaspers.
So anyways, voters, I really want you to vote.
You can choose Flower....
You'd better vote me, or-or I'll stretch you!
- ANNOUNCER: Blocky...
- Come on, guys! I really deserve a third chance.
- ANNOUNCER: Woody...
- Ahh... Ehhh...
- ANNOUNCER: Pin...
- Vote for me, and I will make improvements
to the show of Battle for Dream Island!
- ANNOUNCER: Needy...
- Don't call me Needy!
- ANNOUNCER:
Needy. Needy. Needy.
Teardrop...
- ANNOUNCER:
Golf Ball...
I have a 6.666 repeating
percent chance on joining the game,
and if I rejoin, I'll have a 16.666 repeating
percent chance of winning Dream Island.
So, from this moment, I have a 1.111 repeating
- ANNOUNCER: Coiny...
- Viewers! All you people out there!
I mean, yeah, I love you guys – you're all my
friends – but just-just think for a moment.
Does it really make sense that someone
as stupid as Firey is in the game,
yet someone-someone like me is not?
Just-just think about that for a moment
and the answer will come to you:
the person that you think should win!
- ANNOUNCER: Snowball...
- I'm the only one who really deserves Dream Island!
The rest are all WEAK LOSERS!
- ANNOUNCER: Match...
- OMG!
Vote for, like, me, and plus, I dyed my hair, like, blue.
ANNOUNCER:
Eraser...
Hey! This rejoin button isn't working.
- ANNOUNCER: Pen...
- If you vote for me,
I will give you 500 million
vigintillion dollars!
- ANNOUNCER: That clumsy Tennis Ball...
- You know, Announcer, I wouldn't say that if I were you.
I've got a magnet, and I can DEMAGNETIZE you!
ANNOUNCER:
Yikes!
- ANNOUNCER: Pencil...
- ♪ Vote for me, yeah yeah yeah! ♪
♪ Type my name, yeah yeah yeah! ♪
♪ So I can rejoin the contest, ♪
♪ So I can rejoin the contest! ♪
- ANNOUNCER: and David.
- Aw, seriously?!
- ANNOUNCER: Say something else.
- NO!
Cast a vote by commenting on this video.
I was wondering: how are we in space, yet able
to talk, paddle, breathe, and not explode?
Budget cuts.